Song:hanser
演唱：hanser
Lyricist & Composer:Yunomi
作词&作曲：Yunomi
Engine sound that seems to break Four
壊れそうなエンジン音
Beyond the blue sea Five
青い海を越えて
The passenger plane carrying the two
ふたりを乗せた旅客機は
Dare to crash land
敢えなく不時着
Swaying swaying lifeboat
揺れる揺れる救命ボート
Don't sink
沈まないで
I knocked up a wet skirt Ten
濡れたスカートをたくしあげた
Sandy beach spreading ocean
砂浜 ひろがるオーシャン
No fan if you play alone
ひとりでいじけてたらノー·ファン
Sunshine warm
サンシャインぽかぽか
Premonition of love that bounces to the heart
心まで弾む恋の予感
SOS to rescue team
レスキュー隊へSOS
I can't see the rescue yet
まだ救助は見えないそうです
Two uninhabited islands
ふたりっきりの無人島
Holiday to spend forever
いつまでも過ごすホリデー
I want to dance with you
あなたとあなたと踊りたい
South island
南の島
Midsummer night twenty one
真夏の夜
I won't sleep until morning twenty two
朝まで朝まで眠らない
For a ripe smell twenty three
熟れた匂いに
Wrapped twenty four
包まれる
Dance floor One fruit twenty five
ダンスフロア ひとつぶの果実
I'm sure it's sweet
きっとね 甘いの あまあいの
You cast a spell
あなたが魔法をかけた
Biting a dream
夢をかじるの
This heartbeat that seems to pop
弾けそうなこの心音
The night sky echoes
夜の空響いて
To you back to back
背中合わせのあなたに
Don't realize
悟られないように
One or two flowing stars
ひとつふたつ流れる星
I am looking for
探してる
Please, so that it will arrive someday
おねがい いつの日か届くように
Moonlight that guides the two
ふたりを導くムーンライト
I remember when I was little
小さい頃を思い出すんだ
I'm about to be swallowed by the darkness
暗闇に飲み込まれそうで
Frightened Lonely Night
怯えてるロンリーナイト
It doesn't have to be inevitable
必然じゃなくていいよ
You don't have to say forever
ずっと なんて言わなくていいよ
But hey God, only now
でもねえ神様 今だけは
I want to monopolize
独り占めしたいな
I want to dance with you
あなたとあなたと踊りたい
South island
南の島
Midsummer night
真夏の夜
I won't sleep until morning
朝まで朝まで眠らない
Magic is not yet
魔法はまだ
in the process of
続いている
Dance floor One fruit
ダンスフロア ひとつぶの果実
I'm sure it's sweet
きっとね 甘いの あまあいの
You cast a spell
あなたが魔法をかけた
Biting a dream
夢をかじるの
Someday my love too
そういつか わたしの恋も
I'm sure it's over
きっとねえ 終わるの 終わるの
Until the sun rises again
太陽がまた昇るまでは
Let me dream
夢を見させて